## **IVORY BROWN**

#### **Aspiring Software Engineer**

**510-340-8065** 

ivoryanna.brown@duke.edu

% https://github.com/itb2

**♥** Durham, NC/Bay Area, CA



#### **WHO AM I**

I am someone whose experiences and obstacles in life have made her strong, motivated and resilient. I have a deep love for all things coding and engineering related, but I also enjoy simpler things like Marvel movies, Legos and riding bikes in the city.

### **EDUCATION**

B.S. Computer Science

**Duke University** 

Jan 2015 - ongoing

GPA **3.30** / 4.00

Web Development Intensive

**New York Code and Design Academy** 

GPA
NA / NA

Sep 2016 - Dec 2016

High School Diploma

**Eastside College Preparatory School** 

**May 2010 - May 2013** 

**3.92** / 4.00

## **CURRENT PROJECTS**

#### Web Designer

I took on the responsibility of developing a website to promote the North Carolina Central University's Fabrication Lab

• I am furthering my front and back end web dev and programming skills.

### Black Duke - IOS Development

I am currently working on an app to organize the Black community and Black events at Duke and cater to those interested in social, political and academic issues relevant to the Black community.

• This is my first project in iOS development.

## **LANGUAGES**

**English** 



Spanish



### **TECHNOLOGIES**

#### **Programming Languages**

Java Python Ruby JavaScript
Swift C++

#### Programming/Dev Tools

 Rails
 Sinatra
 Git
 NodeJs

 Vim
 HTML
 CSS
 Xcode

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Web Master

## Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, Inc. | Nu Omicron Chapter

Duke University's Nu Omicron Chapter of Zeta Phi Beta

• I developed and continue to manage our chapter website. This was my first Web Design job which caused me to seek other projects in that area.

## Legal Assistant/ Summer Intern

#### **Rutan & Tucker LLP**

I June 2014 - Aug 2014 Palo Alto, CA

"A full-service law firm based in Costa Mesa, California that is organized into more than 30 legal practice areas in six groups..."

 I learned a great deal about doing research and compiling my my findings in reports for attorneys

# Tech Desk Attendant Stanford University Libraries

May 2013 - Aug 2013 Palo Alto, CA

Meyer Library Tech Desk at Stanford University

 I learned about customer service and troubleshooting issues with technology.